nzclassified.net 2013-11-27

# Privacy Policy - New Zealand Free Classified Ads

NZClassified.net is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. The following policy acts as a guide enabling you to understand how your personal information will be treated when you make use of the site. This policy may change from time to time.

### What kind of personal information will be collected from you?

When you register on NZClassified.net, personal data such as your name, email id, address, phone number etc. are required. On registration you will receive a unique user name that will give you complete access to NZClassified.net In addition we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place ads or use other features of the NZClassified.net

### How is your information used?

NZClassified.net collects your personal information to provide you with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout the website.

### Who collects your information?

The personal information you furnish to NZClassified.net will not be disclosed to anyone unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users.

### With whom do we share your information?

NZClassified.net will not disclose your personal information unless we have your permission or under special circumstances. NZClassified.net may disclose account information only when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of NZClassified.net or if it is causing injury to or interference in rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. NZClassified.net may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

### What are the security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?

Other than the administrator of NZClassified.net or other authorized personnel of NZClassified.net you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password protected to prevent unauthorized access.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. NZClassified.net will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in NZClassified.net This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, NZClassified.net cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us from our online services, you do so at your own risk. However once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

### What else should you know about your online privacy?

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.NZClassified.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

www.NZClassified.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookies

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.NZClassified.net.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.NZClassified.net and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include **Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.NZClassified.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.NZClassified.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.NZClassified.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
